unionpluscard.com 2010-06-21

# HSBC Privacy and Security Policy

Privacy | Privacy Statement | Your Choices to Limit Sharing | Your Choice to Limit Marketing | Security Information | Website Terms and Conditions

HSBC Bank Nevada, N.A., ("HSBC Bank Nevada") is the proud issuer of the Union Plus® Credit Card. We understand the importance of handling customer information in a professional and confidential manner. We know that privacy is an important element of our customers' confidence in us and we understand that our customers expect us to collect and retain personal financial information responsibly. 

Experience

  * HSBC Bank Nevada is a member of a financial family with more than a century of financial experience.

Electronic, Physical and Administrative Safeguards

  * We take great care to ensure your personal information is kept safe.
  * Only carefully trained professionals and companies who service your account or who provide services to you or to us have access to your personal information.
  * HSBC Bank Nevada diligently maintains security measures that comply with applicable federal standards. This assists us in preventing unauthorized access to your non-public personal information.

Responsible Information Sharing

  * Information is sometimes shared within the HSBC Bank Nevada family of Affiliates for purposes that could benefit you such as fraud control and other general business purposes. 
  * We only contract with respectable, carefully screened third-party financial and non-financial companies that offer our customers valuable merchandise and services. 

Control Over Information Sharing and Marketing

  * We give you a choice. If you do not want us to share your information or limit certain marketing, follow our opt-out procedures and we will be happy to comply with your opt-out request, consistent with the procedures in our Privacy Statement. 
  * Click here to view our Privacy Statement.
  * Click here to view Security Information.
  * Click here for information on our use of "cookie" technology.
  * Click here for Website Terms and Conditions.

Top of Privacy  
Back to Top

Introduction - Our Commitment to You | How We Handle Information We Collect | How We Protect Your Privacy Online | How We Share Information within the HSBC Family of Companies  | How We Share Information with Union Privilege, Your Union and the AFL-CIO | How We Share Information with Other Third Parties (Non-Affiliates other than Union Privilege, Your Union and the AFL-CIO)

Introduction - Our Commitment to You

HSBC Bank Nevada, N.A. ("HSBC", "we", "us", or "our") is the proud issuer of The Union Plus Credit Card. HSBC is proud to be part of a financial services organization that has been providing superior products and services for more than 150 years. We greatly appreciate the trust that you and millions of customers have placed in us, and we protect that trust by continuing to respect the privacy of all our applicants and customers even if our formal customer relationship ends. 

This Privacy Statement illustrates our commitment to your privacy and explains our privacy practices to help you understand how we protect and use your information. 

We may change our privacy practices at any time as permitted by law, and if we do so, we will provide you with notice as required. If you have selected a credit-related insurance product, the Privacy Statement applicable to that credit insurance product is set forth at the end of this Privacy Statement. 

Top of Privacy Statement  
Back to Top

How We Handle Information We Collect

It is important for you to know that in order to ensure that our customers get the very best service and the highest quality products, and to develop new products, HSBC collects demographic information (like your name, address, and social security number) and credit information (like information from your application, your credit report or related to your accounts with us). In some instances, we obtain information about you directly from Union Privilege†. In addition, if you visit our website, we may collect certain information about your internet usage. 

Because some of the information we gather is not publicly available, we take great care to ensure that this information is kept safe from unauthorized access, and we will not share the information in violation of any regulation or law. HSBC diligently maintains physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with applicable laws to guard your private personal information and to assist us in preventing unauthorized disclosure or access to that information. 

Top of Privacy Statement  
Back to Top

How We Protect Your Privacy Online

Our website offers you the opportunity to view your current account information and make payments online, in addition to providing general information about our company and products. You may also view our Privacy Statement when you visit our website. 

To help us learn which products, services and sections of our websites interest you, and to improve your experience, we use "cookies." Cookies are small files that our web server places on your hard drive to track activity on the website during a browsing session, and across multiple sessions. We also use cookies to "remember" which online service you last logged into, so that we can preselect that service on your next visit. The cookies we set contain no personal information. Cookies can only track activity on our website, and cannot be read by any non-HSBC websites. 

We may also use online profiling to help us better understand your individual financial needs. This information does not identify you personally unless you voluntarily give us personal information while online. 

We also work with other third parties to learn more about activity on our website. These vendors use "web beacons," "tracking pixels," "third party cookies" and other similar technologies to gather user demographics and usage patterns, which help us improve the effectiveness of our marketing and of our website design. These vendors do not share any personally identifiable information about you. 

Top of Privacy Statement  
Back to Top

How We Share Information within the HSBC Family of Companies

From time to time, for general business purposes or when we think it may benefit you, we share certain information with other companies within the HSBC family of companies (our "Affiliates*"), except as prohibited by applicable law. We may also provide information to Affiliates that perform operational services related to your account(s). These Affiliates all provide financial services, such as banking, consumer finance, insurance, mortgage, and brokerage services. Some examples include companies doing business under the names HSBC, HFC®, Household, or Beneficial®. We may also share certain information with non-financial service providers that become affiliated with us in the future (such as travel, auto, or shopping clubs), except as prohibited by applicable law. The information we share might come from your application, for instance your name, address, telephone number, social security number, and e-mail address. Also, the information we share could include your transactions with us or our Affiliates (such as your account balance, payment history, and parties to the transaction), your internet usage, or your credit card usage. 

Top of Privacy Statement  
Back to Top

How We Share Information with Union Privilege, Your Union and the AFL-CIO

We have an established relationship with Union Privilege and the AFL-CIO. Pursuant to this relationship, we issue credit card offers to members of AFL-CIO affiliated unions. Except for California and Vermont residents, we share certain information about you with Union Privilege, your union and the AFL-CIO so that we and they can provide you with the services and benefits of the Union Plus Credit Card Program and continue to bring you new opportunities. We obtain some information about you directly from Union Privilege. Other information we collect comes from the sources described above. The information we share with Union Privilege, your union or the AFL-CIO includes information we receive from you on your application or other forms such as your name, address, telephone number, income, real property purchased, leased or rented, marital status, dependents and e-mail address, as well as information about your transactions with us, such as the status and usage of your Account, purchase and payment history, including merchants (and/or categories thereof) from whom you have purchased, and marketing preferences. Sharing information with Union Privilege allows them to provide you with information about valuable union benefits and services that are available to you and your family that you might not otherwise hear about. For California and Vermont residents, state law restricts how we share information about you. Accordingly, we will not share information about you in this way without your permission. If we request your permission, we will notify you of the categories of information we would like to share with Union Privilege, your union and the AFL-CIO and the manner in which you can provide us with permission if you choose to do so. 

Top of Privacy Statement  
Back to Top

How We Share Information with Other Third Parties (Non-Affiliates other than Union Privilege, Your Union and the AFL-CIO)

Except for California or Vermont residents, we may share information with companies outside of the HSBC family of companies (i.e. Non-Affiliates) that are able to extend special offers that we feel might be of value to you. These companies may be financial services providers (such as mortgage bankers, insurance agents or a re-insurer) or they may be non-financial companies (such as retailers or marketing companies). These offers are typically for products and services that you might not otherwise hear about. The information that we may provide Non-Affiliates comes from the sources described above and might include your name, address, phone number, and information about your account with us. For California and Vermont residents, applicable law requires us to obtain your permission in order to share information about you with Non-Affiliates, and so we have chosen not to share your information in this way while you are a resident of California or Vermont. 

We may also provide information to Non-Affiliates that perform operational services for your account such as, collection, fraud control and marketing. The sharing of information with these types of Non-Affiliates is permitted by law. This might include a financial company (such as an insurance service provider) or a non-financial company (such as a data processor or Internet service provider) with whom we have a service agreement. The information we may share also comes from the sources described above and might include your name, address, phone number, and account experience with us. 

Finally, we provide information about you to Non-Affiliates as permitted by law. These may include credit reporting agencies and companies which provide services related to your account. 

Top of Privacy Statement  
Back to Top

Privacy | Privacy Statement |  Your Choices to Limit Sharing |  Your Choices to Limit Marketing | Security Information | Website Terms and Conditions

How to Opt-Out of Sharing with Our Affiliates in the HSBC Family of Companies | How to Opt-Out of Sharing with Union Privilege, Your Union and the AFL-CIO (Except for residents of California and Vermont) | How to Opt-Out of Sharing with Other Third Parties (Non-Affiliates other than Union Privilege, Your Union and the AFL-CIO) (Except for residents of California and Vermont) | Your Choice to Limit Marketing | Spanish

How to Opt-Out of Sharing with Our Affiliates in the HSBC Family of Companies

If you do not want us to share your credit report information with our Affiliates (unless we are permitted or required by law to do so), please let us know by simply calling us toll-free at 1-877-876-8819. If you have previously informed us of your preference, you do not need to do so again. This request will not apply to information about your transactions or experience with us (such as account information, account usage, or payment history). This request will only apply to the Union Plus Credit Card account that you designate in your request. 

Top of Your Choices to Limit Sharing  
Back to Top

How to Opt-Out of Sharing with Union Privilege, Your Union and the AFL-CIO (Except for residents of California and Vermont)

If you do not want us to share your non-public personal information with Union Privilege, Your Union and the AFL-CIO (unless we are permitted or required by law to do so), please let us know by simply calling us toll-free at 1-877-876-8819. If you have previously informed us of your preference about this account, you do not need to do so again. This request will only apply to the Union Plus Credit Card account that you designate in your request. 

Top of Your Choices to Limit Sharing  
Back to Top

How to Opt-Out of Sharing with Other Third Parties (Non-Affiliates other than Union Privilege, Your Union and the AFL-CIO) (Except for residents of California and Vermont)

If you do not want us to share your non-public personal information with Non- Affiliate companies (unless we are permitted or required by law to do so), please let us know by simply calling us toll-free at 1-877-876-8819. If you have previously informed us of your preference about this account, you do not need to do so again. This request will only apply to the Union Plus Credit Card account that you designate in your request. 

**How to Limit Affiliate Marketing Offers**

  * Federal law gives you the right to limit some but not all marketing from our Affiliates. Federal law also requires us to give you this notice to tell you about your choice to limit marketing from our Affiliates. 
  * You may limit our Affiliates in the HSBC family of companies, such as our insurance, and consumer finance affiliates, from marketing their products or services to you based on your personal information that we collect and share with them. This information may include your income, your account history with us, and your credit history with us. 
  * Your choice to limit marketing offers from our Affiliates will apply for at least 5 years from when you tell us your choice. If you have previously informed us of your preference, you do not need to do so again within the 5 year period. Once that period expires, you will receive a renewal notice that will allow you to continue to limit marketing offers from our Affiliates for at least another 5 years. 

To limit marketing offers under this section, you must call the toll-free telephone number 1-877-876-8819. 

**Joint Accounts**  
For all opt-out types made available under this Privacy Statement, an opt-out request by any party on a joint account will apply to all parties on the joint account. 

**Notice for Nevada Residents**  
Pursuant to Nevada law, we are providing this notice, which applies to accounts with Nevada mailing addresses, to inform you that you may elect to be placed on our internal "do not call" list. To be placed on the list, you may call us toll free at 1-800-622-2580, or write P.O. Box 80027, Salinas, California, 93912. You may also contact the Bureau of Consumer Protection, Office of the Nevada Attorney General, 555 E. Washington Avenue, Suite 3900, Las Vegas, Nevada 89101. 

**Notice for Vermont Residents**  
HSBC does not share your information with Affiliates, other than information relating to your account transactions and our experiences with you, except as permitted or required by applicable law. 

Spanish

Atención clientes hispanohablantes: Esta Declaración Sobre la Privacidad proporciona información sobre cómo manejamos información personal no publica acerca de nuestros clientes, las circunstancias bajo las cuales podemos compartir tal información con otras personas, y cómo usted puede solicitar que no compartamos esa información con terceros que no sean afiliados nuestros. Si quisiera que le proporcionemos una traducción al español de la Declaración Sobre la Privacidad en su totalidad, por favor llamár al numero indicado al reverso de su tarjeta de credito. 

† Union Privilege was created by the AFL-CIO in 1986 to provide union members and their families with high-quality consumer benefits and services. Union Privilege works with HSBC to provide the benefits and services of the Union Plus Credit Card Program. Union Privilege also has full-time union member advocates who work to helping union members resolve credit card concerns. 

* "Affiliates" are companies that are related to us by common ownership or corporate control. Our Affiliates include companies such as HSBC Bank USA, N.A., HFC®, Beneficial®, Household Insurance Group Holding Company, and HSBC companies such as HSBC Mortgage Corporation (USA), HSBC Credit Centers Inc., HSBC Auto Finance Inc., and Solstice Capital Group.

Top of Your Choices to Limit Sharing | Top of Your Choices to Limit Marketing   
Back to Top

**HOUSEHOLD INSURANCE GROUP HOLDING COMPANY**  
Privacy Statement for Customers with Insurance**

This paragraph applies only to customers with insurance products provided by Household Insurance Group Holding Company ("HIG"). HIG respects and protects your privacy. To administer the insurance requested by you or provided in connection with your account, HIG collects demographic information (like your name and address) and information related to insurance coverage (like information related to your account with HSBC or information related to your health). This information comes either directly from you, for instance from your application, or it may come from HSBC, such as information about your account, or it may come from a credit report or medical information bureau report. HIG takes great care to protect the privacy of this information. For example, the only employees or companies that can access such information are those who need it to provide services in connection with your insurance. Moreover, HIG maintains physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to protect against unauthorized use or disclosure of that information. HIG does not disclose information about you to their respective affiliates or to third parties, except as permitted by law. 

You have a right to see personal information collected about you and the right to correct any information, which may be wrong, by writing to us at the following address: Insurance Customer Service Operations, 90 Christiana Rd., New Castle, DE 19720. 

** Household Insurance Group Holding Company (also under the trade name of HSBC Insurance Services or HSBC Insurance) includes Household Insurance Group, Inc., Household Life Insurance Company, HSBC Insurance Company of Delaware (formerly known as Service General Insurance Company), First Central National Life Insurance Company of New York, Household Life Insurance Company of Delaware, BFC Insurance Agency of Nevada, HSBC Insurance Agency (USA) Inc., and such other companies Household Insurance Group Holding Company may subsequently acquire. 

IN00141

Top of Your Choices to Limit Sharing | Top of Your Choices to Limit Marketing   
Back to Top

Privacy | Privacy Statement |  Your Choices to Limit Sharing | Your Choices to Limit Marketing | Security Information | Website Terms and Conditions

We understand that security is a prime concern for our customers, and our website strives to offer a high level of security:

  * All Internet access must be completed using a browser that supports SSL encryption. All communications between you and our website are encrypted by a 128 bit secure link to protect the confidentiality of your data. State of the art monitoring systems and firewalls are used to prevent unauthorized access to our systems.
  * Users are required to select their own Login ID and Password when they sign up, and can change it at any time. 
  * The website will automatically log off after a period of inactivity during any session to protect your information.
  * Only carefully trained professionals and companies who service your account have access to your personal information.
  * We diligently maintain security measures that comply with applicable federal standards.

Top of Security Information  
Back to Top

Website Terms And Conditions

Copyright and Other Intellectual Property | Limited Liability | NO WARRANTIES | Links | Children | Confidentiality of Information | Information and Cookies | Choice of Law | Website Content and Material | Waiver and Severability | Access to Secured Areas

Copyright and Other Intellectual Property

HSBC Bank Nevada, N.A., or its corporate parents, affiliated companies, or subsidiaries (collectively "HSBC Bank Nevada" and/or its Affiliates") is the owner or the authorized user of this website and certain other websites linked to the site, as well as all text, images, graphics, photos, animation, music, sounds and other materials contained within these websites.

The materials contained within these websites, including, without limitation, any copyrights, trademarks, service marks, and all other proprietary materials, are protected by the U.S. and international copyright laws and treaty provisions, trademark laws, and other proprietary rights laws. The material contained within these websites is provided by HSBC Bank Nevada and/or its Affiliates only for lawful uses by customers, employees, and members of the general public. The material may not be copied, republished, incorporated into another website or reproduced (whether by linking, framing, or any other method), transmitted, distributed, uploaded, posted, used to create a derivative work or exploited in any other way without the express written consent of HSBC Bank Nevada.

HSBC holds a license to practice U.S. Patent Nos. 6,405,181; 6,567, 181; and 7,143,063.

Top of Website Terms and Conditions  
Back to Top

Limited Liability

NEITHER HSBC BANK NEVADA, ITS PARENT, AFFILIATES OR SUBSIDIARIES, OR ANY OTHER PARTY INVOLVED IN THE CREATION, PRODUCTION OR DELIVERY OF THE INFORMATION AT THIS SITE, NOR THE OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES OR REPRESENTATIVES OF ANY OF THE FOREGOING, ARE LIABLE IN ANY WAY FOR ANY DIRECT, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, CONSEQUENTIAL, OR INDIRECT DAMAGES (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION LOST PROFITS, COST OF PROCURING SUBSTITUTE SERVICE OR LOST OPPORTUNITY) ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THIS SITE OR THE USE OF THIS SITE OR A LINKED SITE OR WITH THE DELAY OR INABILITY TO USE THIS SITE OR A LINKED SITE, WHETHER OR NOT HSBC BANK NEVADA IS MADE AWARE OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. THIS LIMITATION INCLUDES, BUT IS NOT LIMITED TO, THE TRANSMISSION OF ANY VIRUSES, TROJAN HORSES OR HARMFUL CODE THAT MAY AFFECT A USER'S EQUIPMENT, ANY INCOMPATIBILITY BETWEEN THIS SITE'S FILES AND THE USER'S BROWSER OR OTHER SITE ACCESSING PROGRAM, FAILURE OF ANY ELECTRONIC OR TELEPHONE EQUIPMENT, COMMUNICATION OR CONNECTION LINES, UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS, THEFT, OPERATOR ERRORS, OR ANY FORCE MAJEURE. HSBC BANK NEVADA DOES NOT GUARANTEE CONTINUOUS, UNINTERRUPTED OR SECURE ACCESS TO THIS SITE OR A LINKED SITE. THE CONTENT, ACCURACY, OPINIONS EXPRESSED, AND OTHER LINKS PROVIDED BY THE LINKED SITES ARE NOT INVESTIGATED, VERIFIED, MONITORED OR ENDORSED BY HSBC BANK NEVADA. THE INFORMATION, SOFTWARE, PRODUCTS AND DESCRIPTION OF SERVICES PUBLISHED ON THE SITE OR A LINKED SITE MAY INCLUDE INACCURACIES OR TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS, AND HSBC BANK NEVADA SPECIFICALLY DISCLAIMS ANY LIABILITY FOR SUCH INACCURACIES OR ERRORS. CHANGES ARE PERIODICALLY MADE TO THE INFORMATION ON THE SITE AND LINKED SITES. HSBC BANK NEVADA MAY MAKE IMPROVEMENTS OR CHANGES TO THE SITE AT ANY TIME.

Top of Website Terms and Conditions  
Back to Top

NO WARRANTIES

ALL PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND CONTENT ON THIS SITE ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, SECURITY, OR ACCURACY. NEITHER HSBC BANK NEVADA NOR ITS PARENT, AFFILIATES OR SUBSIDIARIES ENDORSES AND NONE ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR THE ACCURACY OR RELIABILITY OF ANY INFORMATION ON THIS SITE. IT IS THE RESPONSIBILITY OF THE USER TO EVALUATE THE ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, TIMELINESS AND COMPLETENESS OF ANY INFORMATION AVAILABLE ON THIS SITE. HSBC BANK NEVADA SPECIFICALLY DISCLAIMS ANY DUTY TO UPDATE THE INFORMATION ON THE SITE.

USER AGREES TO INDEMNIFY, DEFEND, AND HOLD HSBC BANK NEVADA HARMLESS FROM ANY LIABILITY, LOSS, CLAIM AND EXPENSE, INCLUDING ATTORNEY'S FEES RELATED TO A USERS VIOLATION OF THESE TERMS OF USE OR THE USE OF THE SERVICES AND INFORMATION PROVIDED AT THIS SITE. 

Top of Website Terms and Conditions  
Back to Top

Links

Clicking on certain links within this website or certain other websites that are linked to this website may take you to other websites, or may display information on your computer screen from other websites, which are not maintained by HSBC Bank Nevada. Such websites may contain terms and conditions, privacy provisions, confidentiality provisions, or other provisions that differ from the terms and conditions applicable to this website. Links to other Internet services and websites are provided solely for the convenience of users. A link to any service or website is not an endorsement of any kind of the service or website, its content, or its sponsoring organization.

HSBC BANK NEVADA AND ITS CORPORATE PARENTS, AFFILIATES, AND SUBSIDIARIES ASSUME NO RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY WHATSOEVER FOR THE CONTENT, ACCURACY, RELIABILITY OR OPINIONS EXPRESSED IN A WEBSITE, TO WHICH THIS SITE IS LINKED (A "LINKED SITE") AND SUCH LINKED SITES ARE NOT MONITORED, INVESTIGATED, OR CHECKED FOR ACCURACY OR COMPLETENESS BY HSBC BANK NEVADA. IT IS THE RESPONSIBILITY OF THE USER TO EVALUATE THE ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, TIMELINESS AND COMPLETENESS OF ANY INFORMATION AVAILABLE ON A LINKED SITE. ALL PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND CONTENT OBTAINED FROM A LINKED SITE ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, SECURITY, OR ACCURACY.

Top of Website Terms and Conditions  
Back to Top

Children

HSBC Bank Nevada does not knowingly market to, or solicit, or collect personal information from children under age 18.

Top of Website Terms and Conditions  
Back to Top

Confidentiality of Information

HSBC Bank Nevada has taken reasonable steps to ensure the confidentiality of information taken at this website and transmitted via the Internet. HSBC Bank Nevada uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. During an SSL session, data passed back and forth between your computer and the HSBC Bank Nevada online card server is secured by using public key cryptography. Your computer exchanges key information with HSBC Bank Nevada computers to create a private conversation that only your computer and HSBC Bank Nevada's system can understand. However, unexpected changes in technology may be used by unauthorized third parties to intercept confidential information and we cannot be responsible should confidential information be intercepted and subsequently used by an unintended recipient. 

Top of Website Terms and Conditions  
Back to Top

Information and Cookies

HSBC Bank Nevada may collect and receive the URL you came from, the pages of HSBC Bank Nevada website that were viewed during a visit, the advertisements you clicked, any search terms that you entered to reach our site, and certain other information regarding your internet use. See HSBC Bank Nevada's Privacy Statement for how this information may be used, click here to view **Privacy Statement**. Some of HSBC Bank Nevada's websites may also make use of "cookie" technology to measure site activity, determine how you arrived at our site and maintain your identity as you navigate through the website. HSBC Bank Nevada's websites require cookies to allow you to view your statements and transactions online. A cookie is an element of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then store the cookie on your hard drive. Cookies make visiting a website easier for you by saving your preferences while you are at the site. The use of cookies is an industry standard and you will find them at many websites. HSBC Bank Nevada uses the information from cookies to provide services that are customized to your needs.

HSBC Bank Nevada may also use third party advertising companies to serve HSBC Bank Nevada's ads on the Internet. These third party advertising companies also employ cookie technology to measure the effectiveness of ads. To do so, these companies may use information about your visits to HSBC Bank Nevada's website and other websites. Unless otherwise notified, these advertising companies do not use names, addresses, e-mail addresses or telephone numbers, and do not link any online actions or cookies to an identifiable person. The use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policy. 

If you want to prevent a third party advertiser from sending and reading cookies on your computer, currently you must visit each ad network's website individually and opt-out. 

Top of Website Terms and Conditions  
Back to Top

Choice of Law

All website activity or use and these Terms and Conditions are governed by the laws of the United States of America and the laws of the State of Nevada, without regard to conflict of law principles.

Top of Website Terms and Conditions  
Back to Top

Website Content and Material

The information and materials contained in this website, including but not limited to these Terms and Conditions and any product information, are subject to change without notice. Users are deemed to be apprised of and bound by any such changes. Not all products and services are available in all geographic areas. Your eligibility for particular products and services is subject to final determination and acceptance by HSBC Bank Nevada. 

Top of Website Terms and Conditions  
Back to Top

Waiver and Severability

Any waiver of any provision contained in these Terms and Conditions shall not be deemed to be a waiver of any other right, term or provision of these Terms and Conditions. If any provision in these Terms and Conditions shall be or become wholly or partially invalid, illegal or unenforceable, such provision shall be enforced to the extent it is legal and valid and the validity, legality and enforceability of the remaining provisions shall in no way be affected or impaired thereby.

Top of Website Terms and Conditions  
Back to Top

Access to Secured Areas

Access to and use of password protected and/or secure areas of this website is restricted to authorized users only. Unauthorized persons attempting to access these areas of the website may be subject to prosecution.

Updates: These Terms and Conditions were last updated May 1, 2009. Please check periodically for changes.

Top of Website Terms and Conditions  
Back to Top

The following annual notice is being provided to you, because you are enrolled in HSBC Card Services’ Online Bill Payment Service for your general purpose credit card. This notice provides important information regarding the procedures for notification on any errors or questions about your online bill payments.

 **This is not a notification of an error on your account.**

Please read the notice below and retain it for your records.

====================================================== 

**Notice of Error Resolution Procedures**

In Cases of Errors or Questions About Your Electronic Transfers 

  * Telephone us at the number on the back of your credit card, or
  * Write us at HSBC Bank Nevada, N.A. / HSBC Bank USA, N.A., 1441 Schilling Place, Salinas, CA 93912

as soon as you can, if you think your statement or receipt is wrong or if you need more information about a transfer listed on the statement or receipt. We must hear from you no later than 60 days after we sent the FIRST statement on which the problem or error appeared. 

  1. Tell us your name and account number (if any).
  2. Describe the error or the transfer you are unsure about, and explain as clearly as you can why you believe it is an error or why you need more information.
  3. Tell us the dollar amount of the suspected error.

If you tell us orally, we may require that you send us your complaint or question in writing within 10 business days. 

We will determine whether an error occurred within 10 business days after we hear from you and will correct any error promptly. If we need more time, however, we may take up to 45 days to investigate your complaint or question. If we decide to do this, we will credit your account within 10 business days for the amount you think is in error, so that you will have the use of the money during the time it takes us to complete our investigation. If we ask you to put your complaint or question in writing and we do not receive it within 10 business days, we may not credit your account. 

For errors involving new accounts, point-of-sale, or foreign-initiated transactions, we may take up to 90 days to investigate your complaint or question. For new accounts, we may take up to 20 business days to credit your account for the amount you think is in error. 

We will tell you the results within three business days after completing our investigation. If we decide that there was no error, we will send you a written explanation. You may ask for copies of the documents that we used in our investigation. 

Top of Notice of Error Resolution Procedures  
Back to Top

Privacy  |   Privacy Statement  |   Your Choice to Limit Sharing  |   
Your Choice to Limit Marketing  | Security Information  |   Website Terms and Conditions  |     
Notice of Error Resolution Procedures
